Guide to the the Richard W. Lyman, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0215
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Series 1
  - EDUCOM, Stanford Synchrotron Radiation Program, G3.19.12 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - EDUCOM, Teaching Evaluations, G3.19.12 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - EDUCOM, Board of Trustees, G3.19.12 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Iran, G3.19.12 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - China, 3/73-8/76; G5.2 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Report, Change Magazine, 1977; O1 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 6/74-8/76; O3.1 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - American Council on Education, 11/73-8/76; O3.8 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 2/76-8/76; O3.10 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 2/75-8/76; O3.92 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Assn, 8/75-8/76; O3.44 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - National Assn. of College and University Business Officers, 10/73-8/76; O3.55 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Other Universities & Colleges, 11/75-8/76; O8 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Association of American Universities, 7/75-8/76; O8.7 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - AAU: Executive Committee, 9/75-8/76; O8.7.3 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - University of California, 9/72-8/75; O8.43 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Research, miscellaneous, 7/69-8/76; R0 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Research Administration, 11/75-8/76; R1 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Research, Vice Provost for:, 6/75-8/76; R1.1 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Research, 10/68-8/76; R1.2 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research, 11/72-8/76; R1.4 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Energy Studies, 3/73-8/76; R1.4.2 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Solar Energy Research Institute, R1.4.3 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - SERI. Meeting, 4/5/76; R1.4.4 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Solar Energy Research Institute, 10/75-8/76; R1.4.4 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Synchrotron Radiation Project, 1/75-8/76; R1.9 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - NMR Lab, 11/72-8/76; R1.10 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Proposals (misc.), 9/73-8/74; R4 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - ASSU, General, St2 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - ASSU Senate, 3/72-5/76; St2.0 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Miscellaneous / Stanfordiana, AD1 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Governor Stanford Locomotive, AD1.1 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Academic Administrative Information Projects, AD1.6.2 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Annual Reports (Administrative and Academic), AD1.6.3 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Policy: Authorizations / signing, etc, AD1.6.5 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Procedures, AD2.10 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Liquor Policy, AD2.15 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Resolutions, Memorial and other, AD2.16 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Pets on Campus, AD2.20 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Religion, AD2.24 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - ROTC file #1, AD2.26 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - ROTC file #2, AD2.26 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Guide, AD3.2 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Campus Reports, AD3.4 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - University Calendar / Holidays, AD3.21 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Speeches: Richard W. Lyman, 1970-72; AD3.22 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Speeches (other than RWL). [FILE MISSING - NO OUT CARD], AD3.22 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - President, AD4.1 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - President's House, Staff, Car, AD4.1 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - A - C general and miscellaneous, AD4.20 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - D - H general and miscellaneous, AD4.20 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - I - N general and miscellaneous, AD4.20 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - O - S general and miscellaneous, AD4.20 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - T - Z general and miscellaneous, AD4.20 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, AD4.20.4 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Complaints I, AD4.20.5 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Complaints II, AD4.20.5 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Complaints III, AD4.20.5 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Recommendations Letters (routine), AD4.20.6 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - University Relations, 5/24-11/76; AD4.22 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Legal Problems and Services, AD7 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - DOS Case Numbers, AD7.2.5 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Cost of Campus Disruptions, AD7.2.6 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Dismissal Cases, AD7.5 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Founding Grant, AD7.6 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Judicial Procedures / Charter, AD7.9 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Legal Cases, AD7.10 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Participation in Politics, Policy on, AD7.13 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Admissions Office, AD8.1 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Policy: Admissions general, AD8.1.1 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Admissions Cases:, 1976 (June and earlier); AD8.1.2 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Conferences, AL1.7 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - The Stanford Magazine, AL1.12 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Associates, AL2 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Clubs miscellaneous, AL3.4 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - New Founder's League, AL4.4 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees Elections, B4 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees Manual, B5 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees By-Laws, 1968-72; B7 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees By-Laws, 1973-; B7 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Cabinet, B9 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees Reorganization, B10 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Trustees Appointments and Resignations / membership roster, B12 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Trustee Role and Appointment Criterion, B12.1 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Agenda and pre-Board Agenda, B13.3 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Additional Matters (Board of Trustees), B13.5 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Trustee Committees, B14 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Finance and Development Committee, B14.4 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Committees, Commissions, Administrative Panels, etc, C (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council Minutes / Reports, C1 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Academic Council Correspondence, C1.1 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Senate Reports by Numbers, C2.4 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Board Meetings, C3.2 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Board, Rules for Conduct of Hearings, C3.4 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Senate Committees, C4 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Committees (Correspondence), C4.2.1 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Members of Academic Council to attend ASSU Senate Meetings as Stanford Guests, C4.4 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Study of Graduate Education at Stanford (SGES), C4.5 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement (C-AAA), C5.1 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Committee on Academic Standing, Petitions and Exceptions (C-AAA-ASPE), C5.1.1 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Committee on Evaluation of Teaching (C-AAA-TE), C5.1.2 (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - Gores-Dinkelspiel, 1959-75; C5.1.3 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - The Rhodes-Marshall Panel (C-AAA-RMP), C5.1.4 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, C5.3 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Admissions and Financial Aids (file #1), C5.6 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Admissions and Financial Aid (file #2), C5.6 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Committee on Female Admissions, C5.6.1 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Special Joint Agency for the Program in Urban Studies, C5.7.4 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Joint Agency on Stu. Inn. [sic] Committee on Undergraduate Studies and Dean of Undergraduate Studies, C5.8 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Special Joint Agency of the C-US and D-US on SWOPSI, C5.9 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Panel on Internal Athletic, Physical Education and Recreation Programs (PIAPERP), C6.2 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Land and Buildings, C6.3.1 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Computational Facilities, Committee on, 6/72-8/76; C6.3 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Minority Affairs, Committee on, C6.7 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Services to Students, C6.9 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Human Relations Commission, C7.5 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Commission on International Studies, C7.6 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Committee Policies / General information, C7.12 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Task Forces I to VI -UBPAC, (1975); C7.13.1 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Parking and Transportation, C8.1 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Radiological Hazards Control Committee, C8.2 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - SLAC Coordinating Committee, C8.4 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Library Council, C8.5 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Panel on the Use of Human Subjects in Research (PUSHR), C8.7 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Panel on Health and Safety, C8.10 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Panel on Laboratory Animal Care (APLAC), C8.11 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Legislative and Judicial Bodies for Student Conduct, C9 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Campus Judicial Panel Hearing Officers (for cases see AD 7.2.4), C9.1 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Committee of Fifteen, C9.2 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Search Committees, miscellaneous, C12 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Directorship (Search Committee), C12 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Search File: Registrar.[RETREIVED BY THE PRESIDENT'S OFFICE 5/0/79], C12 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Search Committee for the Assistant to the President for Chicano Affairs. [RETREIVED BY THE PRESIDENT'S OFFICE 5/0/79], C12 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Dean of Humanities and Sciences Search Committee, C12 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - Academic Secretary: Search Committee, C12 (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Assistant to the President: Search [RETREIVED BY THE PRESIDENT'S OFFICE 5/0/79], June-Sept. 197(?); C12 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - ATP-TA Search File (large envelope), 1977; C12 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Chicano Affairs Search (large envelope), C12 (cross filed at: AD 9.2.1) (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Search File: Vice-Provost and Dean of Undergraduate Studies (large envelope), C12 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - California State Government, G1.2 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - California State Commission for Teacher Preparation and Licensing, G1.3.1 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - California Education Facility Authority, G1.3.2 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - California Post-Secondary Education Commission, G1.3.5 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Federal Legislation, G3.1 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Herbert Amendment, G3.1.16 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), G3.7.4 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), G3.8 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - HEW: Office for Civil Rights, G3.8.1 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - National Institute of Health, G3.8.2 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - HEW Report on Higher Education (Newman), G3.8.3 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - HEW: Office of Education, G3.8.4 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - National Science Foundation, G3.19 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - National Medal of Science, G3.19.11 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - EDUCOM, G3.19.12 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Central Intelligence Agency [MKULTRA documents and cover letter], 1977; G3.27 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Palo Alto, City of: Community Relations, G4.2 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Stanford/Palo Alto Community Liaison, G4.2.1 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Countries, Governments, etc, G5 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - China visit, G5.2.1 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Ad hoc and miscellaneous organizations, O1 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Boy's Town Center, O1.10 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission: SU Committee, O1.20 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - World Affairs Council, O1.31 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Industry - Education Council of California, O1.38 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Corporate Support of American Universities, Committee for, O2.2 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Research Institute. File #1, O2.11 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Research Institute. File #2, O2.11 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - University Study Group, O3.5 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - American Association of University Professors, O3.6 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - A.C.E. Administrative Internship Program, O3.8.1 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Carnegie Commission on Higher Education, O3.22 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - College Entrance Exam Board, O3.25 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Institute of International Education, O3.38 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - PAC-8 Conference Meetings, O3.47.3 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - PAC-8 Conference Meeting Minutes, O3.47.3 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Financial Aspects of the Athletic Programs/Reviewing Committee/Financial Aid to Athletes, O3.47.3 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Intercollegiate Comp. for Women/Right of Women to compete on Men's teams (PAC-8), O3.47.3 (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Ethnic Minority Officials. (PAC-8 conference), O3.47.3 (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - Rose Bowl, O3.47.3 (Box 126, Folder 19)
  - 1.6 Rule (PAC-8 Conference), O3.47.3 (Box 126, Folder 20)
  - Freshman eligibility for Varsity football & basketball issue, O3.47.3 (Box 126, Folder 21)
  - Financial Statements/Income Summaries (PAC-8), O3.47.3 (Box 126, Folder 22)
  - PAC-8 Meeting (R.W. Lyman), 1974; O3.47.3 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, O3.51 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - University Research Association, O7.16 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Association of American Colleges, O8.6 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - A.A.U.: Council on Federal Relations, O8.7.1 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - A.A.U.: Council on Federal Regulations, O8.7.1 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Association of Governing Boards and Universities, O8.8 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Association of Independent California Colleges and Universities, O8.9 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Cornell University, O8.19 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Harvard University, O8.2.3 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - International Association of Universities, O8.25 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Princeton University, O8.36 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Inaugurations, O8.55 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics (SIAM), O8.57 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Solar Energy Research Institute (SERI), R1.44 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Indirect Costs, 10/73-8/76; R3.1 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Research Development Fund, R3.2 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Research Development Fund, R .2 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - R.D.F. Awarded, R3.2.1 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Research Proposals (miscellaneous), R4 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - National Iranian Radio-T.V. (NIRT) Contract, 9/76-12/77; R4.8 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Advanced Research Projects Agency, R5.6 (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Students, miscellaneous, St.1 (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - ASSU: Budget, Fees, Financial Problems, St2.1 (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - ASSU: Constitution, St2.2 (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - ASSU: Committee on Nominations, St2.7 (Box 128, Folder 15)
  - ASSU: Council of Presidents, St2.8 (Box 128, Folder 16)
  - Student Activities, St3 (Box 128, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Band, St3.4 (Box 128, Folder 18)
  - KZSU (Radio Station), St3.18 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Student Publications, St3.23 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Daily, St3.23.7 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Workshops on Political and Social Issues (SWOPSI), St3.28 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - SCIRE: Student Center for Innovation in Research and Education, St3.30 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - ARLO: Action Research Liaison Office, St4.1 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Free Campus Movement, St4.8 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Student Deaths, St5.2 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Freshmen, St5.3 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Cases handled by the SJC: A - B (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Cases handled by the SJC: C - E (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Cases handled by the SJC: F - H (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Cases handled by the SJC: I - L (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Cases handled by the SJC: M - P (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Cases handled by the SJC: Q - S (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Cases handled by the SJC: S - Z (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Associates of American Universities, 9/72 - 6/73 (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Academic Appointments, AA1.3 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Deans Council Correspondence, AA1.5 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Academic Leadership Conference/Deans Retreat, AA1.5.3 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Academic Planning Office, AA1.7 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Dean of the Chapel, AA1.8 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Office of Undergraduate Studies, AA1.12 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Division, AA1.13 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - National Board on Graduate Education, AA1.13.1 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Faculty, Miscellaneous (loyalty oaths), AA2 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Paulsen, Jim, AA2 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Napier, Dean of the Chapel, AA2 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Articles of Organization of the Faculty, AA2.1.1 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Emeriti, AA2.2 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Appointments, AA2.3 (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Faculty and Academic Appointment Procedures and Policies, AA2.3.2 (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Academic Freedom, AA2.6.1 (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - Franklin Case: File #1, AA2.6.2/1 (Box 130, Folder 17)
  - Franklin Case: File #2, AA2.6.2/1 (Box 130, Folder 18)
  - Franklin Case: Petitions File #1, AA2.6.2/1 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Franklin Case: Petitions File #2, AA2.6.2/1 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Franklin, H. Bruce, AA2.6.2/1 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Tenure: Policy, 4/72-8/76; AA2.6.9 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Volunteer Leadership Conference (GSO), AA2.7.1 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Academic Standing/Requirements, AA3.5 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Ph.D. Review Committee Report, AA3.10.1 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Summer Sessions, AA3.16 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Specials, AA3.18.3 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, AA4.1 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Values, Technology and Society, AA4.1.1/1 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Locomotive (Duplicate File Art Department), 1/9/63-9/21/76; AA4.1.9 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Art and Architecture, AA4.1.9 (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Rodin Collection/Cantor Gift, AA4.1.9/1 (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Linguistics, AA4.1.11 (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - Communications, AA4.1.15 (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Professional Chandler Center for Journalism, AA4.1.15/1 (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - Football Games: 1975-1976, 1975-8/1976; AA4.1.30/1 (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - Freshman Eligibility, AA4.1.30/4 (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - Women's Physical Education, AA4.1.31 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Business School: Sloan Program, AA4.2.1 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - School of Engineering.[Folder Missing - No OUT card], AA4.4 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Engineering, AA4.4.6 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - School of Education, AA4.5 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Department of Psychiatry, AA4.6.14 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Medical Practice, AA4.6.17 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Sherman Fairchild Center for the Neurosciences, AA4.6.18 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Addiction Research Laboratory, AA4.7 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Hoover Institution - Confidential, AA4.9 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Hoover Institution, AA4.9 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Hoover Institution: Board of Overseers, AA4.9 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Hoover Institution: Policy, AA4.9 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Japanese Studies at Stanford, AA4.10.2 (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Status of Librarians, AA4.12 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - School of Law, AA4.15 (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Hospital: Board of Directors, AA4.17.2 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Center for Information Processing, AA4.22 (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - Awards and Prizes, Miscellaneous, 6/74-8/76; AA5 (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - White House Fellows, AA5.4 (Box 132, Folder 20)
  - Scholarships, Miscellaneous, AA7 (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - Heritage Fund, AA7.11 (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - National Merit Scholarships, 1971-74; AA7.19 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Fellowships, Miscellaneous/General, 1972-75; AA8 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Guggenheim Fellowship Awards, 1973-76; AA8.17 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Harry Camp Memorial Lectures, 1972-75; AA9.7 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Sloss Visiting Lectureship, 1971-75; AA9.18 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Ford Foundation Professorships in International Studies, 1971; AA10.18 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Trouble/Complaints, 1965-71; AD4.20.5 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Troubled: Hopkins, Wilma, AD4.20.5 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Gregman File (President's Office), AD4.20.5 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Troubled: Gantner, Vallejo, AD4.20.5 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Troubled: Fischer, Marguerite, AD4.20.5 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Calsoyas, AD4.20.5 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Coulter, James, AD4.20.5 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Schiffman, Max, AD4.20.5 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - SJC #4 Trustees Meeting, 1/14/69; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - SJC #13 Encina Hall, 5/1/69; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - SJC #32 Rock Throwing, Weiss and McGuire, 3/31/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - SJC #32 McGuire, Diarmind, Rock Throwing, 3/31/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - SJC #32 Weiss, Janet, Rock Throwing, 3/31/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 19)
  - SJC #33 Sweeney, Mike, 5/1/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 20)
  - SJC #37 McGuire, D., Academic Council, 4/3/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 21)
  - SJC #37 Everdell, Peter B., Academic Council, 4/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 22)
  - SJC #37 Erickson, Leif Charles, Charges Dropped, 11/20/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 23)
  - SJC #37 Gostovich, John B., Charges Dropped, 11/20/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 24)
  - SJC #37 Keitch, John, Charges Dropped, 11/20/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 25)
  - SJC #37 Sweeney, Michael, Charges Dropped, 11/20/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 26)
  - SJC #37 Fischer, Francois, Charges Dropped, 11/20/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 27)
  - SJC #37 Gocking, Roger Stephen, Charges Dropped, 11/20/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 28)
  - SJC #37 Gustafson, Albert K., Charges Dropped, 11/20/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 29)
  - SJC #37 Parks, David, Charges Dropped, 11/20/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 30)
  - SJC #37 Shoch, John F., Charges Dropped, 11/20/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 31)
  - SJC #37 Weiss, Janet Margaret C., Charges Dropped, 11/20/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 32)
  - SJC #37 Broderick, Tim, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 33)
  - SJC #37 Denenholz, Cynthia, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 34)
  - SJC #37 Douglas, W. Otto, Closed, 10/15/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 35)
  - SJC #37 Fisher, Francois, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 36)
  - SJC #37 Fleeson, George, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 37)
  - SJC #37 Hammond, Rich, Closed, 10/15/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 38)
  - SJC #37 Goetz, Lori, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 39)
  - SJC #37 Hanson, Mary, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 40)
  - SJC #37 Katzenbach, Chris, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 41)
  - SJC #37 Johnson, Scott. Encina Door Blocking, 11/15/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 42)
  - SJC #37 Lowe, Fichard S, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 43)
  - SJC #37 Levin, Lanny, Encina Door Blocking, 5/11/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 44)
  - SJC #37 McNamara, Craig, Encina Door Blocking, 5/11/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 45)
  - SJC #37 Marks, Alfie, Closed JS, 10/15/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 46)
  - SJC #37 Moore, Roberta, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 47)
  - SJC #37 Oswald, Nancy, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 48)
  - SJC #37 Otto, Steve, Closed JS, 10/15/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 49)
  - SJC #37 Pollock, Bruce, (1) Closed, 10/15/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 50)
  - SJC #37 Pollock, Bruce, (2) Closed, 10/15/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 51)
  - SJC #37 Schindler, Craig, Closed, 10/15/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 52)
  - SJC #37 Shea, Pat A., Closed, 10/15/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 53)
  - SJC #37 Weiss, Marc, Closed, 10/15/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 54)
  - SJC #37 Bows, Robert A., Closed, 10/15/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 55)
  - SJC #37 Atkins, Richard N., Closed, 10/15/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 56)
  - SJC #37 Barber, James L, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 57)
  - SJC #37 Bauer, Anne C., Academic Council, 4/3/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 58)
  - SJC #37 Siegel, L., Academic Council, 4/3/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 59)
  - SJC #37 SJC: Academic Council, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 60)
  - SJC #38 Old Union Sit-in, 4/23/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 61)
  - SJC #38 Old Union, 4/23/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 62)
  - SJC #39 SJC: Old Union, 4/29/70; AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 63)
  - SJC #40 Grossman, Henry, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 64)
  - SJC #41 Malicious Mischief, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 65)
  - SJC #42 ROTC Door Blocking, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 66)
  - SJC #43 Rock Throwing: W.E. Hamburg, AD7.2.4 (Box 133, Folder 67)